Guide to the Washington Area Women's Center records, 1868-1989 MS2344
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Organizations, 1968-1984; Series 2
  - Coalition of Gay Sisters (COGS), Columbia, MD, 1977-1979; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Columbia, Maryland, 1977-79
  - Commission on the Status of Women, 1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Congress to Unite Women, 1969; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    New York, 1969
  - Congressional Union, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Abortion Rights Coalition [Planned Parenthood], 1981; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Washington, D.C., 1981
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Committee Baake Decision, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Committee CETA Funding, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Washington, D.C. and Includes "An Evening in Solidarity with Zimbabwe" and March on Supreme Court
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Events, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Financial Reports, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Herstory amp;amp; Description, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Members, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Members' Informal Notes, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Minutes amp;amp; Agendas 1977-78, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Minutes amp;amp; Agendas 1979-1981, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Newsletters, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Position Papers, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Standing Committee Reports, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Structure amp;amp; Bylaws, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Structure amp;amp; Bylaws, comments on, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Subgroup Politics, 1977; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Washington, D.C., 1977
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Task Force Communications, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Task Force Physical Requirements, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Washington, D.C.; includes IWY
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Task Force Political, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Task Force Skills, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Task Force Structure amp;amp; Process, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Task Force Violence Against Women, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance: Two Day Meeting, 1978 September 16 - 17; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Washington, D.C., 9/16-17/1978
  - D.C. Area Feminist Chorus, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Washington, D.C., 1981-82
  - D.C. Coalition for Women, 1979; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Washington, D.C., 1979 includes a GWU reference
  - D.C. Different Drummers, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Feminists Against Pornography, 1980; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Front Runners, 1981; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Hags, 1979; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - D.C. International Women's Year [IWY] Coordinating Committee, 1977-78; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Washington, D.C., 1977-78
  - D.C. National Organization for Women (NOW), 1977-1980; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Washington, D.C., 1977-1980
  - D.C.SAGE [Senior Action in a Gay Environment], 1982; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Washington, D.C., 1982
  - D.C. Task Force on Abused Women, 1976; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Task Force on Women amp;amp; Alcoholism, 1980; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Women's Collective, 1983; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Washington, D.C., 1983
  - D.C. Women's Law Coalition, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Women's Political Caucus, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Dialog for Human Rights, D.C., 1977-1978; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Diana Press, Inc., 1979; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Oakland, California, 1979
  - Dignity, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Dykes Against Racism Everywhere (D.A.R.E.), undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Washington, D.C.,
  - Eastern Region Producers, 1981; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Catonsvile, Maryland, 1981
  - Equinox Productions, 1981; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Federally Employed Women, Inc. (FEW), 1970-1977; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Washington, D.C., 1970-77
  - Feminist Alliance Against Rape, Inc. [includes info on their magazine AEGIS], 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Feminist Anti-Nuclear Task Force, undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Washington, D.C. and [later renamed Hunter, Polikoff, Bodley amp;amp;amp; Bottum, P.C.]
  - Feminist Fridays, 1984; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Washington, D.C., 1984. See also audiotapes
  - Feminist Law Collective, D.C., 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Feminist Radio Network, 1974-1976; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Washington, D.C., 1974-76; formerly knowns as the October 17th Movement
  - Feminists, The, 1968-1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    New York, 1968-70
  - Fine Line: An Actor's Theatre, Washington, D.C., 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Washington, D.C., 1981; Notebook inventory List of Books for Women
  - First Things First [1/2], 1973-1977; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Washington, D.C., 1973-1977,
  - First Things First [2/2], 1973-1977; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Washington, D.C., 1973-77
  - First Women's Bank of Maryland, 1977-1978; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Rockville, Maryland, 1977-78
  - FIST: Feminists Insist on a Safe Tomorrow, 1980; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Philadelphia, PA; 1980
  - Friday Night Live, 1988-1982; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Washington, D.C., 1988-82
  - Gay & Lesbian Switchboard, 1983; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Gay AA & Al-Anon D.C., 1979; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Gay Activists Alliance of Washington, D.C., 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Gay & Lesbian Pride Day/Week, 1982; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Gay Community Center, D.C., 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Gay People of Georgetown University, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Washington, D.C., 1980-81
  - Gay Peoples Alliance: GWU, undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1980; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Gay Women's Alternative, D.C., 1981-1983; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Washington, D.C., 1981-83
  - George Washington University Women's Liberation, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Washington, D.C., 1971-72
  - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club, 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Gray Panthers of Metropolitan Washington, 1983; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Growing Women Collective, 1976-1980; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Washington, D.C., 1976-80
  - Hallowmas Women Writers, The, 1980; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - High amp;amp; Dry, 1983; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Iris Glen Camp, 1980; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    near Annapolis, MD, 1980
  - Karen Silkwood Fund, undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - KNOW, 1971; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Pittsburgh, 1971
  - Lammas Women's Shop, 1974-1983; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Washington, D.C., 1974-83; name chanted in 1981 to Lesbian Resource amp;amp;amp; Counseling Center (LRCC)
  - Lesbian Health & Counseling Center, 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Washington, D.C., 1979-80; name changed in 1981 to Lesbian Resource amp;amp;amp; Counseling Center (LRCC)
  - Lesbian Resource & Counseling Center, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Community Church, 1977-1982; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Washington, D.C., 1977-1982
  - Metropolitan Ministry with Women, 1976; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Moonforce Media, undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - National Coalition of Black Gays, Inc., 1980; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - National Gay Task Force, 1979; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - National March on Washington for Lesbian amp;amp; Gay Rights, 1979; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - NOW D.C. Sexuality Task Force, 1975-1980; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Greater Washington Area, 1975-80
  - OWLS, 1981; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Washington area, 1981
  - Parents of Gays, Washington, D.C., 1976; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Pre-Birth Clinic, undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Prince George's County Commission for Women, 1978-1981; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Upper Marlboro, MD, 1978-81
  - Pro Femina Theatre, undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Washington, D.C.; see separate box 5
  - Quest, undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Washington, D.C.; based in WAWC but separate group
  - Rape Crisis Center, D.C., undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights, 1976-1982; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Washington, D.C. amp;amp;amp; New York, 1976-82
  - Reston Gay Rap Group, RG2, 1980; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    Reston, VA, 1980
  - Richmond Lesbian Feminists, undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    Richmond, VA
  - Rising Women Collective amp;amp; Coffeehouse, 1975-1976; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    Arlington, VA, 1975-76
  - Roadwork, 1978-1983; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Washington, D.C., 1978-83
  - Rural American Women, Inc. (RAW), 1977-1978; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    1977-78; formerly Saphire's Sappho
  - Sapphire Sapphos, 1980-1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Washington, D.C., 1980-82; includes Survey of G.W. Office Workers
  - Sixty Words Per Minute (60wpm), 1977-1978; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Washington, D.C., 1977-78; head org: Toronto Canada
  - Sophie's Parlor, 1977; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - W.I.T.C.H. (with many meanings for intitials), 1968-1970; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Washington, D.C., 1968-70
  - Wages for Housework Committee, 1980-1982; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Toronto, Canada, 1980-82
  - Washington Area Feminist Federal Credit Union (WAFFCU), 1975; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Washington, D.C., 1975; see audiotapes
  - Washington Area Feminist Theatre (WAFT), undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Washington Professional Women's Cooperative, 1978-1980; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Washington, D.C., 1978-80
  - Washington Women Outdoors, Inc., 1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Washington Women's Art Center, 1979; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Washington D.C. Women's Business and Cultural Center, 1977; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Washington Women's Self-Help, undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - WATER: Women's Alliance for Theology, Ethics and Ritual, 1983; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Well Deserved Promotions, undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Whitman-Walker Clinic, Inc., 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Washington, D.C., 1979-80
  - Wider Opportunties for Women (WOW), 1973-1981; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Washington, D.C., 1973-81
  - Woman Sound, 1979-1983; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Washington, D.C., 1979-83
  - WomanAlert, 1978; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Woman's Legal Defense Fund, undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Women in Community Service, Inc., undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Washington, D.C.; includes 1975 and 1978 catalogs
  - Women in Distribution, 1975-1979; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Washington, D.C., 1975-79; formerly Throttle Witches
  - Women in Gear, undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Women Musican's Cooperative, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Washington, D.C., 1980-1981
  - WOAR: Women Organized Against Rape, undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Women Strike for Peace, 1980; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Women's Liberation Zap Action Brigade Express, undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Washington, D.C.; Started by Mary Farmer, owner of Lammas
  - Women's Music Express, 1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Women's Pentagon Action, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - WomynLovers, 1981; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Oakland, Calif., 1981
  - Yolanda Ward Memorial Fund, undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Quest "Gerri", undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Quest Meeting Minutes Etc., undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Published Manuscript: Jo Delaplaine, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Published Manuscript: Allie Corbin Hixson, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Published Illustrations: Inga Ford, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Published Manuscript: Ginny Crow, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Published Manuscript: Marie Nahikian, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Published Manuscript: Laura Punnett, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Published Manuscript: Mary Therese Riccio, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Published Manuscript: Dorothy Riddle, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Women and Appropriate Technology, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Newsletters, 1969-1989; Series 3
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains newsletters. These records have a date range of 1969-1989.
  - D.C. Women's Liberation: List of Current Women's Liberation Material, 1969; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: D.C. Women's Liberation Bulletin, 1970: January - September 19; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    [alternate titles: Women's Liberation News, D.C. Women's Liberation Information Bulletin, and Women's Liberation Bulletin]
  - Newsletters: Washington Area Women's Center Bulletin, 1972 January to December; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters: Washinton Area Women's Center Newsletter, 1973 January to June; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters: Washinton Area Women's Center Newsletter, 1973 July to December; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters: Washington Area Women's Center Newsletter, 1974 January, February, March, July; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters: Washinton Area Women's Center Newsletter, 1975 April to December; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1976 October and December and 1977 January to December; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1978 January to December; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1979 January to December; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    In Oct '79 issue, pg. 3, see "missing issues report".
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1980 January to December; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1981: January to December; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1982 January to December; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1987 July/August, Sept, October; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Gap with missing issues from December '82 to July '87
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1988 January to December; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters: In Our Own Write, 1989 January to June; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Abortion Material, 1971; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Abortion: D.C. Clinics, undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Subject files, 1970-1971; Series 4
  This series contains files that Center volunteers used to assist clients and for other projects. These records have a date range of 1970-1971.
  - Abortion: Anti-Abortion Info, 1971; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Abortion: D.C. Clinics, Undated; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Abortion: General No. 1, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Abortion: General No. 2, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Abortion: Pre-Term Clinic, 1970-1971; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Adoption, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Advertising: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Archives: Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Art and Women Artists, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Assertive Training, Undated; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Battered Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Bibliographies: KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Bibliographies: Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Black Women and Feminism, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Black Women: General Info, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Birth Control, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Books and Periodicals: Feminist, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Bookstores and Booksellers, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Businesses: Feminist, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Cable TV and Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Child Abuse, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Child Care / Day Care, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Children, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Class, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Communes, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Conferences: Feminist, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Conferences: Lesbian, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Consciousness Raising, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Consumer Services and Aid, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Credit and Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Crime, Undated; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Government and Local Issues, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Dance, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Deaf Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Disabilities: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Discrimination, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination: D.C. Title 34, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Discrimination: EEOC Sex Discrimination Guidelines, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Discrimination: Housing, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Displaced Homemakers, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Divorce and Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Draft: Women and the, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Ecology, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Economics: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Education: Affirmative Action, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Education: Continuing, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Education: Discrimination, Undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Education: Elementary School, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Education: Financial Aid/Fellowships, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Education: General, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Education: Higher - General, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Education: Legislation, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Education: Minority Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Education: Title IX, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Education: Vocational, Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Education: Women's Studies (General), Undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Employment: U.S. Women's Bureau, Undated; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Energy, Undated; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Energy: Nuclear, Undated; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), Undated; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - ERA: News Clippings, Undated; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Events (cultural, etc.), Undated; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Film: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Government: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Grand Jury Info, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Group Houses, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Health: General, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Health: Cancer Information, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Health: DES [diethylstilbestrol], Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Household Workers, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Women, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Land: Women Only, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: National March on Washinton 1979, Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Lesbian Bars, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Lesbian Separatism, Undated; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Lesbians: General, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Military: Women [servicewomen, spouses], Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Music: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Photography: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Politics [not covered by other subject files], Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Publishers: Feminist Lesbian, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Religion, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Sexuality: Heterosexuality, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Sexuality: Survey Forms, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Theater: Women and, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Women's Centers, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - "Selections from the Fourth World Manifesto", Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - "Some Things to Worry About", Undated; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Reprints, 1868, 1920, 1966-1980; 1966-1980; Series 5
  This series contains article reprints. The bulk of these records are in the date range 1966-1980.
  - Aberle, Kathleen Gough; Anthropology And Imperialism; New England Free Press, Undated; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Alaniz, Yolanda; An Independent Force for Unity; Radical Women, Undated; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Anne and Jacqueline; From One Group to Another (1972); ©Maspero, Paris; International Feminist Translators, Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Anthony, Nicole; Open Letter to Psychiatrists; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Anthony, Susan B., et al; The Revolution, January 22, 1868; KNOW, Inc., 1868 January 22; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - April; Covert Sexual Discrimination Against Women in Psychological Contexts: As Clients (1972); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Association for Women Psychologists; Psychology and the New Woman: Statement of the Association for Women Psychologists to the American Psychological Association, 1970; Sepember 1970, Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Atkinson, Ti-Grace; The Institution of Sexual Intercourse; Radical Feminism (1969); Radical Feminism and Love (1969); Vaginal Orgasm as a Mass Hysterical Survival Response (1968); The Feminists, NY, NY, 1968-1969; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Babcock, Barbara, Ann Freedman, Eleanor Holmes Norton, Susan Deller Ross and friends; Women and the Law: A Collection of Reading Lists (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Bacon, Margaret; Woman as Peacemakers; American Friends Service Committee, Undated; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Bailey, Mary; Women are a Traditional Society (also in Spanish); International Feminists Task Force, 1973, Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Barclay, William, Joseph Enright and Reid T. Reynolds; Population Control in the Third World; Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Barry, Herbert III; Cross Cultural Perspectives on How to Minimize the Adverse Effect of Sex Differentiation; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Barry, Kathleen; The Cutting Edge: A Look at Male Motivation in Obstetrics and Gynecology (1972), Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 28)